<doctrines>
	mode=		The deployment mode the unit will adopt.  Note that
				this influences the presence of ZOC, rate of march,
				etc.
	role=		The combat role that a unit must have in order to 
				adopt this doctrine.  If not defined, any eligible 
				unit type can use the doctrine.
	adfRate=	Attacking Direct Fire Rate.  This is the multiple applied to
				the weapons rate multiple when the weapon participates
				in direct combat.
	aifRate=	Attacking Indirect Fire Rate.  This is the multiple applied to
				the weapons rate multiple when the weapon participates
				in artillery fire.
	ddfRate=	Defending Direct Fire Rate.  This is the multiple applied to
				the weapons rate multiple when the weapon participates
				in direct combat.
	difRate=	Defending Indirect Fire Rate.  This is the multiple applied to
				the weapons rate multiple when the weapon participates
				in artillery fire.
	aRate=		Advance Rate.  This multiple is applied to the retreat
				interval of the defenders.  A more aggressive doctrine will
				capture a hex sooner than a less aggressive or effective
				doctrine would.
	aacRate=	When Attacking, Attacker Casualty Rate.  This multiple is applied to the 
				attacker's casualties incurred during a combat.  Note that
				this rate applies for both attacking and defending doctrines.
				Thus an aggressive attack doctrine against an effective 
				defensive doctrine will yield combined increases in casualties.
	adcRate=	When Attacking, Defender Casualty Rate.  This multiple is applied to the
				defender's casualties incurred during a combat.  Like the acRate,
				the dcRate is defined for both offensive and defensive doctrines
				and will yield combined results.
	dacRate=	When Defending, Attacker Casualty Rate.  This multiple is applied to the 
				attacker's casualties incurred during a combat.  Note that
				this rate applies for both attacking and defending doctrines.
				Thus an aggressive attack doctrine against an effective 
				defensive doctrine will yield combined increases in casualties.
	ddcRate=	When Defeinding, Defender Casualty Rate.  This multiple is applied to the
				defender's casualties incurred during a combat.  Like the acRate,
				the dcRate is defined for both offensive and defensive doctrines
				and will yield combined results.

	<doctrine doc=attack name="Attack" code=A
		mode=attack
		role=attdef
		adfRate=.9
		aifRate=1
		aRate=1
		aacRate=1.5
		adcRate=1.1
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1.5
        requiresUse
	 />
		- A popular old-school attack style favored by WW I and less sophisticated WW II nations
		- Note that this is taken as the 'standard' offensive doctrine rates, against which
			
	<doctrine doc=wave name="Human wave attack" code=wA
		mode=attack
		role=attdef
		adfRate=.9
		aifRate=1
		aRate=1
		aacRate=1.5
		adcRate=1.1
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1.5
	 />

		- Essentially invented by the Germans in 1916, this is the most sophisticated
			assault technique available, but it is costly

	<doctrine doc=infil name="Infiltration Attack" code=iA
		mode=attack
		role=attdef
		adfRate=1
		aifRate=1
		aRate=1
		aacRate=1
		adcRate=1
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1.5
        requiresUse
	 />

		- This is the German Blitzkrieg assault appropriate for German combined arms attacks

	<doctrine doc=keil name="Keil und Kessel Attack" code=kA
		mode=attack
		role=tac
		adfRate=1
		aifRate=1
		aRate=1.5
		aacRate=1.1
		adcRate=1.1
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1.5
        requiresUse
	 />

		- This type of assault is typical of American WW II units relying on heavy arty and
			air support and conserving losses.

	<doctrine doc=cautious name="Cautious attack" code=cA
		mode=attack
		adfRate=.8
		aifRate=1
		aRate=.5
		aacRate=.9
		adcRate=.9
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1.5
	 />

		- Another cautious form of combat, this will yield an advance only if the defenses 
			are extremely weak.

	<doctrine doc=probe name="Probing attack" code=pA
		mode=attack
		adfRate=.7
		aifRate=.8
		aRate=.3
		aacRate=.7
		adcRate=.7
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1.5
	 />

		- A typical order for quiet sectors.  This form of combat does not try to advance,
			but merely terrorizes and bleeds the opposition: appropriate for artillery units

	<doctrine doc=harass name="Harassment fire" code=hA
		mode=attack
		role=art
		adfRate=0
		aifRate=.1
		aRate=0
		aacRate=0
		adcRate=.5
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1.5
	 />

    - A typical order for artilery units supporting an assault

    <doctrine doc=barrage name="Barrage" code=bA
		mode=attack
		role=art
		adfRate=0
		aifRate=1
		aRate=0
		aacRate=0
		adcRate=.8
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1.5
	 />

	<doctrine doc=defend name="Defense" code=D
		mode=defend
		aRate=1
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1
        requiresUse
	 />

		- A defensive order used with less sophisticated troops.

	<doctrine doc=fixed name="Fixed defense" code=fD
		mode=defend
		aRate=1
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1
	 />

    - The standard defensive doctrine used whenever the strength of the defenders is
    enough.  A defense in depth will generally be able to hold a position as long as
    available reserves hold out.

    <doctrine doc="depth" name="Defense in depth" code="dD"
		mode="defend"
		aRate="1"
		ddfRate=1
		difRate=1
		dacRate=1
		ddcRate=1
	 />

    - This defense is adopted when numbers are not sufficient to hold the position with
    a proper defense in depth.

    <doctrine doc="around" name="All-around defense" code="aD"
		mode="defend"
		aRate="1"
		ddfRate=1
		difRate=1
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1
	 />

    - This defense is adopted when the defenders want to yield ground when attacked,
    conserving strength and minimizing losses, but giving ground

    <doctrine doc=screen name="Screen" code=sD
		mode=defend
		aRate=2
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1
	 />

		- This mode expends fuel and ammo in field exercises, and produces some wear and tear,
			but improves the experience of the unit's staff

	<doctrine doc=training name="Training" code=T
		mode=training
		aRate=.9
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1
	 />

    - This mode minimizes resource consumption and wear and tear.  It also revives fatigue.

    <doctrine doc="rest" name="Rest" code="R"
		mode="rest"
		aRate=".7"
		ddfRate=".5"
		difRate=".5"
		dacRate=".8"
		ddcRate="1"
	 />

    - This mode disperses the unit into adjacent hexes to protect facilities and combat
    partisans.

    <doctrine doc=security name="Security" code=S
		mode=security
		aRate=.9
		ddfRate=.5
		difRate=.5
		dacRate=.8
		ddcRate=1
	 />

    <doctrine doc="command" name="Command" code="C"
		mode="command"
		role="hq"
		aRate="1"
		ddfRate=".5"
		difRate=".5"
		dacRate=".8"
		ddcRate="1"
	 />

    <doctrine doc="entrain" name="Entrained" code="E"
		mode="entrained"
		aRate="1"
		ddfRate=".25"
		difRate=".1"
		dacRate=".8"
		ddcRate="3"
	 />

	<doctrine doc=move name="March" code=M
		mode=move
		aRate=1
		ddfRate=.25
		difRate=.25
		dacRate=1
		ddcRate=2
	 />

</>